newswire.net 2014-03-30

# Newswire.net - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement

This website is the property of **Newswire Network Ltd ("Newswire")**.

Our postal address is:

Newswire Network Ltd   
2089 E Fort Union Blvd  
Salt Lake City, UT 84121 

Newswire takes privacy seriously. As a leader in online visibility and search engine optimized press release distribution services, we are committed to establishing and maintaining policies and procedures which protect the privacy of personal information gathered from our customers, prospects and other visitors to our website.

Newswire is a news service which distributes press releases and other news content (“Article”) on behalf of our users. In addition, Newswire users are allowed to create other kind of pages, including business profile, personal profile, and other pages that may contain user supplied personal information. The information that you supply in these profile pages may, according to the settings that you supply, be available to the public.

If you decide to submit an Article for distribution through our system we will transmit your entire Article including any personal information therein contained to our media contacts and online distribution points including search engines. This is the only redistribution of your information that we engage in. Your submission of an Article through our system indicates consent with this policy.

This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Newswire.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, you may contact us at [support@newswire.net](mailto:support@newswire.net). In order for Newswire to take the appropriate action please describe in reasonable detail the nature of your request or inquiry.

### Personal Information Privacy:

We do not share user supplied information with any third parties other than via press release distribution, and the display of user supplied information on our website, as described above.

### Cookies and Data Utilization:

Newswire employs Google Analytics and/or other third party features (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, etc.). Newswire may also employ remarketing scripts with Google Analytics and/or others to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show Newswire ads on sites across the Internet to you, based on your visit to our site.

Newswire and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website.

Newswire and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to your site.

Newswire may use data from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data from Google Analytics, or others, to display customized advertising or articles that it may believe are of interest to you, based on your age, gender or expressed interests.

### Opting out of Data Collection:

Newswire users who disable their web browser's ability to accept cookies may not be able to successfully use our service.

Using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads.

Users may manage all Google Analytics access, both on Newswire, and elsewhere by checking [currently available opt-outs](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) for the web.

### Changes to Personal Information:

We provide site visitors with access to information that we have collected and that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by logging into their user account.

### Third-Party Sites:

The site contains links to other websites. Newswire is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites. You will need to check the policy statement of other websites to understand their policies. Customers and visitors who access a linked site may be disclosing their private information. It is the responsibility of the user to keep such information private and confidential.

### Security:

With respect to security, we employ industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving user data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. We do not store credit card information in our systems.

### Changes to Privacy Statement:

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change in the future, we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. To keep up-to-date with Newswire policy, please check this page periodically.

### Contacting the Website:

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us by sending us an email to [support@newswire.net](mailto:support@newswire.net).
